Guide to the Papers of Marcos Sanchez-Tranquilino and Holly Barnet-Sanchez relating to the CARA exhibition (Chicano Art Resistance and Affirmation, 1965-1985), 1986-1990
Department of Special Collections
Sanchez-Tranquilino, Marcos. Papers of Marcos Sanchez-Tranquilino and Holly Barnet-Sanchez relating to the CARA exhibition (Chicano Art Resistance and Affirmation, 1965-1985),
1986-1990
M0666
Sanchez-Tranquilino, Marcos
3 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Access Terms
Barnet-Sanchez, Holly; CARA; Chicano Art Resistance and Affirmation; CARA National Advisory Committee; Art, Modern--20th century; Mexican American arts; Mexican Americans; Mexican American artists. lcsh
Collection Contents
- Papers: Chicano (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Chancellor's Challenge Grant (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NEH Reviews on CARA (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Various Images, Photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Budgets and Other Schedules (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Women's Exhibition: Jacinto's Essay (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Development - general CARA (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CARA Dev.: CAC (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Info. on Centros (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Education (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Curriculum Development (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Complimentary Programs Off-Campus (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Articles: Newspapers (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CARA: Travel and Venues (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Writings on CARA by Mts. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Meetings with Tomas Y-F 1988 Aug 16, Exhibit Model and NEH proposal (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence by M & H (Box 1, Folder 17)
- CARA artists' statements (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Info: Stanteros [ie Santeros] (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Memos to M & H (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Wight Gallery Meetings (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CARA Weekly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 1990 Aug 29 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Fax to Mexico Permissions (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Tonelli (Box 1, Folder 25)
- L.A. Festival (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Supplemental Programs: UCLA (Box 1, Folder 27)
- "Timelines" Subcommittees by Regions (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Publicity: On and Off-Campus (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Chicano Art 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Chicano Screen Print Taller WAG & Self-Help Graphics in conjunction w/ CARA 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- CARA Taller (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CARA Implementation Meeting 1989 Dec 15 - 1989 Dec 16 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Editorial Board Meeting 1989 Mar 11 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Meeting 1 1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Chicano Planning Conference 1986 Nov 7 - 1986 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Docents, Gallery Shop, Art Council (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Time Line Materials: Clues, etc. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Non-Muralist Artists (Box 1, Folder 39)
- CARA Selection Committee Meeting 1989 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- National Selection Committee meeting II 1988 Sept 6 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Mel Casas, San Antonio, Texas (Box 1, Folder 42)
- CARA Honorary Committee (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Newsletters: CARA (Box 1, Folder 44)
- SFMOCA Fiasco (Box 1, Folder 45)
- National Selection Committee Meeting 1989 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- CARA: SF (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Call for Papers - mailing lists (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Interpretive Components: mural slides, mural video, artists video (Box 2, Folder 4)
- CARA Mural Checklist Final 1990 Nov (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CARA events (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Incoming & Outgoing Phone Calls re. WAG Chicano Art Exhibit 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Editorial Board and Essays (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Process Essay (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Catalogue (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Interpretive Stations (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Thematic Text Panels (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Installations: RCAF, ASCO, etc. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- CARA CAT Timeline (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Timeline: Articles, resources (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Illustrations for 1345-1965: timeline & captions & citations, originals (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Timeline: exhibition (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Interpretive Components: extended label copy (Box 2, Folder 18)
- HR Design presentation (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Letterhead and Folder Design: CARA (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Poster: CARA Exhibition (Box 2, Folder 21)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: Section IV.A - V (Copy1) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: Section VI - IX (Copy 1) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: Section IV.A - V (Copy 2) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: Section VI - IX (Copy 2) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: a (Box 1, Folder 26)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: b (Box 1, Folder 27)
- NEH Implementation Grant, 3rd Application: c (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Duplicates (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Exhibition Planning Time Line 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Festival 1990 Sept 1 - 1990 Sept 16, program (Box 3)
- Duplicates, Videocassette (Box 3)
- Duplicates, Videocassette (Box 3)
- Duplicates, Videocassette (Box 3)
- Pre-Columbian and Colonial Events and Culture 1345 -1599, Exhibit Panel